A Guide to the Peter F. Geithner papers FA1408
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Professional and personal files, second run, 1951-2011; 2; 18.02 Cubic Feet About 40 LTR size Hollinger boxes and 6 LGL size Hollinger boxes
  - Columbia University Weatherhead East Asian Institute Conference – China's Economic Emergence: Progress, Pitfalls, and Implications a Home and Abroad program, 2005 (Box 97, Folder 1251)
  - National Committee on U.S.-China Relations (NCUSCR) - Breakfast discussion correspondence, 2005 March 14 (Box 97, Folder 1252)
  - Sarasota, Florida and Hilton Head, South Carolina visits, 2005 (Box 97, Folder 1253)
  - American Enterprise Institute for Public Policy Research (AEI) Panel Discussion – Europe, China, and the Arms Embargo: The Implications of Sino-European Partnership for American Interests, 2005 (Box 97, Folder 1254)
  - Sundays at the Snow Library Series, Orleans, Massachusetts, 2004-2005 (Box 97, Folder 1255)
  - National Committee on U.S.-China Relations (NCUSCR) Board of Directors Meeting, 2006 November 2 (Box 97, Folder 1256)
  - National Committee on U.S.-China Relations (NCUSCR) Executive Committee Meeting, 2006 (Box 97, Folder 1257)
  - National Committee on U.S.-China Relations (NCUSCR) Executive Committee Meeting, 2007 (Box 97, Folder 1258)
  - National Committee on U.S.-China Relations (NCUSCR) Board of Directors Meeting, 2006-2007 (Box 97, Folder 1259)
  - National Committee on U.S.-China Relations (NCUSCR) Board of Directors Meeting, 2005 (Box 97, Folder 1260)
  - Bangkok, Thailand trip, 2005 (Box 97, Folder 1261)
  - Bandaranaike Center for International Studies (BCIS) - Lakshman Kadirgamar Memorial Conference on India-China Relations, 2005 (Box 97, Folder 1262)
  - Bandaranaike Center for International Studies (BCIS) - Lakshman Kadirgamar Memorial Conference on India-China Relations, undated (Box 97, Folder 1263)
    Original folder only contained one business card.
  - Columbia University Weatherhead East Asian Institute - Legacies of Change in Southeast Asia: A Festschrift in Honor of John Bresnan, 2005-2006 (Box 97, Folder 1264)
  - National Committee on U.S.-China Relations (NCUSCR) - China NPO Leaders Study Tour, 2005 (Box 97, Folder 1265)
  - Japan Foundation Center for Global Partnership (CGP) - Intellectual Exchange grant proposals, 2005 (Box 98, Folder 1266)
  - Harvard University John F. Kennedy School of Government Panel Presentation - Higher Education in Vietnam: Peril and Promise, 2005 June 24 (Box 98, Folder 1267)
  - America in Question: Korean Democracy and the Challenge of Non-Proliferation on the Peninsula Workshop presentation materials, 2005 (Box 98, Folder 1268)
  - America in Question: Korean Democracy and the Challenge of Non-Proliferation on the Peninsula Workshop, 2004-2005 (Box 98, Folder 1269)
  - Harvard University Asia Vision 21, 2005 (Box 98, Folder 1270)
  - Northeast High School Classes of 1950 55th Anniversary Reunion, 2005 (Box 98, Folder 1271)
  - Northeast High School Alumni Association, 2004-2005 (Box 98, Folder 1272)
  - Horizon Research Consultancy Group - Current Status and Futures Prospects for Sino-African Co-operation, 2007 September (Box 98, Folder 1273-1274)
  - University of Stellenbosch Centre for Chinese Studies (CCS) - China's Engagement of Africa: Preliminary Scoping of African Case Studies, 2007 November (Box 98, Folder 1275-1276)
  - Rockefeller Foundation - China-Africa project, 2007-2008 (Box 98, Folder 1277)
  - University of Stellenbosch Centre for Chinese Studies (CCS) - Monitoring the Forum on China-Africa Cooperation (FOCAC) Commitments, 2007-2008 (Box 98, Folder 1278)
  - Rockefeller Foundation - China-Africa project, 2007-2008; File contains a CD labeled Horizon Research - China-Africa Report. (Box 98, Folder 1279)
  - Horizon Research - China-Africa Report CD (Box 98, Folder 1279)
  - Sasakawa Peace Foundation (SPF) consultancy appointment, 2005-2006 (Box 98, Folder 1280)
  - Sasakawa Peace Foundation (SPF) consultancy appointment, 2005-2006 (Box 98, Folder 1281)
  - Sasakawa Peace Foundation (SPF) consultancy appointment, 2000-2003 (Box 99, Folder 1282)
  - Sasakawa Peace Foundation (SPF) consultancy appointment - Expenses, 1999-2007 (Box 99, Folder 1283-1284)
  - Rockefeller Foundation consultancy appointment - Regional Southeast Asia Strategy, 2001 (Box 99, Folder 1285)
  - Rockefeller Foundation - Philanthropy in Pakistan and India, 2000-2004 (Box 99, Folder 1286)
  - Longquan Treasured Sword pamphlet, undated (Box 99, Folder 1287)
  - Resumes, 1984-1996 (Box 99, Folder 1288-1292)
    Restricted - personnel material
  - Recruitment, 1990-1995 (Box 100, Folder 1293-1294)
  - Ford Foundation - Personal correspondence, 1991-1995 (Box 100, Folder 1295-1296)
  - Ford Foundation report on Vietnam, 1991 (Box 100, Folder 1297)
  - Ford Foundation - Overview of Southeast Asia Program report, circa 1991 (Box 100, Folder 1298)
  - Ford Foundation Office for Asia and the Pacific Program Review background materials, 1979 (Box 100, Folder 1299-1300)
  - The Aspen Institute - The Chinese in the Global Community Seminar, 1995-1996 (Box 100, Folder 1301)
  - Ford Foundation day minder, 1995 (Box 100, Folder 1302-1303)
  - Ford Foundation day minder, 1994 (Box 100, Folder 1304-1305)
  - Ford Foundation day minder, 1993 (Box 101, Folder 1306-1307)
  - Ford Foundation day minder, 1992 (Box 101, Folder 1308-1309)
  - Ford Foundation travel log notebook, 1991 January-May (Box 101, Folder 1310)
  - Ford Foundation notebook, circa 1991 (Box 101, Folder 1311)
  - Harvard-Yenching Institute (HYI) Board of Trustees Meeting, 2005 (Box 101, Folder 1312)
  - Harvard-Yenching Institute (HYI) Board of Trustees Meeting, 2005 (Box 101, Folder 1313)
  - Harvard-Yenching Institute (HYI) Board of Trustees Meeting, 2007 (Box 101, Folder 1314)
  - Harvard-Yenching Institute (HYI) Board of Trustees Meeting, 2007 (Box 101, Folder 1315)
  - Harvard-Yenching Institute (HYI) Board of Trustees Meeting, 2006 (Box 101, Folder 1316)
  - Harvard-Yenching Institute (HYI) Board of Trustees Meeting, 2007 (Box 101, Folder 1317)
  - Harvard-Yenching Institute (HYI) Board of Trustees Meeting, 2006 (Box 101, Folder 1318)
  - Harvard-Yenching Institute (HYI), 2009 (Box 101, Folder 1319)
  - Harvard-Yenching Institute (HYI) Review Report, 2003 (Box 101, Folder 1320)
  - China's Christian Colleges and the Founding of the Harvard-Yenching Institute, Paul Daniel Waite and Peichi Tung Waite, 2004 June 14 (Box 101, Folder 1321)
  - Harvard-Yenching Institute (HYI) External Review, 2008 (Box 101, Folder 1322)
  - Harvard-Yenching Institute (HYI) Internal Review, 1967-2008 (Box 102, Folder 1323)
  - China Medical Board (CMB) Strategy Paper, 2007 (Box 102, Folder 1324)
  - China Medical Board (CMB) Report, 2008 (Box 102, Folder 1325)
  - China Medical Board (CMB) Endowment Fund Report, 2005 (Box 102, Folder 1326)
  - The Lancet - Health System Reform in China, 2008 October (Box 102, Folder 1327)
  - China Medical Board (CMB) Endowment Funds - Chinese Grantees, 2005 (Box 102, Folder 1328)
  - Reconsidering Rockefeller Philanthropy in Republican China, Mary Brown Bullock, 2008 (Box 102, Folder 1329)
  - China Medical Board (CMB) endowment funds - Thailand grants, 1984-1997 (Box 102, Folder 1330)
  - China Medical Board (CMB) endowment funds - Grants, 2003-2009 (Box 102, Folder 1331)
  - China Medical Board (CMB) - Sample award letters, guides, and information regarding international grants management, 1994-2008 (Box 102, Folder 1332-1333)
  - Yale-China Health Journal - China's Health System: From Crisis to Opportunity, 2004 (Box 102, Folder 1334)
  - China Social Entrepreneur Foundation, 2007-2008 (Box 102, Folder 1335)
  - Chinese philanthropy organizations and training programs, 2007-2009 (Box 103, Folder 1336-1337)
  - Japan Center for International Exchange (JCIE) - New Delhi, India meetings, 2007 November (Box 103, Folder 1338)
  - University of Pennsylvania Center for the Advanced Study of India (CASI)/Observer Research Foundation (ORF) Conference - Power Realignments in Asia: A U.S.-India Policy Dialogue, 2006-2007 (Box 103, Folder 1339-1340)
  - University of Pennsylvania Center for the Advanced Study of India (CASI)/Observer Research Foundation (ORF) Conference - Power Realignments in Asia: A U.S.-India Policy Dialogue, 2006 (Box 103, Folder 1341-1343)
  - African Economic Research Consortium (AERC) - Workshop on the Impact of China and India (the Asian Drivers) on Sub-Saharan Africa, 2007; File contains 4 still images. The photographs depict Peter F. Geithner and other individuals at the African Economic Research Consortium (AERC) Workshop on the Impact of China and India (the Asian Drivers) on Sub-Saharan Africa in Mombasa, Kenya. The names of the other individuals have been written on the back of some of the photographs. (Box 103, Folder 1344)
  - Japan Foundation Center for Global Partnership (CGP) - Intellectual Exchange grant proposals, 2006-2007 (Box 103, Folder 1345)
  - India, Thailand, Burma visits, 2006-2007 (Box 103, Folder 1346-1347)
  - University of Pennsylvania Center for the Advanced Study of India (CASI)/Observer Research Foundation (ORF) - Power Realignments in Asia: China, India, and the U.S., circa 2006-2007 (Box 103, Folder 1348)
  - John D. and Catherine T. MacArthur Foundation - An Asian Security Research Agenda Meeting, 2007 (Box 104, Folder 1349)
  - University of Stellenbosch Centre for Chinese Studies (CCS) - The Knowledge Bridge between China and Africa, 2007; File contains a CD version of the University of Stellenbosch Centre for Chinese Studies - China's Engagement of Africa: Preliminary Scoping of African Case Studies Working Paper. (Box 104, Folder 1350)
  - University of Stellenbosch Centre for Chinese Studies (CCS) - China's Engagement of Africa: Preliminary Scoping of African Case Studies Working Paper CD (Box 104, Folder 1350)
  - Rockefeller Foundation - China-Africa Project Launch, South Africa, 2007 (Box 104, Folder 1351)
  - Jonathan and Katie Moore wedding anniversary party, 2007 (Box 104, Folder 1352)
  - Conference on Alternative Development and Sufficiency Economy, undated (Box 104, Folder 1353)
  - National Institute of Development Administration (NIDA) correspondence regarding H.R.H Princess Maha Chakri Sirindhorn of Thailand, undated (Box 104, Folder 1354)
  - China Leadership Monitor, No. 16 - The New Common Economic Program: China's Eleventh Five Year Plan and What it Means, undated (Box 104, Folder 1355)
  - Conference on Alternative Development and Sufficiency Economy, 2005-2007; File contains a still image of Peter F. Geithner talking to another individual. The photograph was likely taken at the Conference on Alternative Development and Sufficiency Economy. (Box 104, Folder 1356)
  - Harvard University Asia Center - Informality, Poverty, and Growth: Labour Markets in China and India Research Design Workshop, 2007 (Box 104, Folder 1357)
  - Harvard University China-India Development and Relations Symposium (CIDRS), 2006-2007 (Box 104, Folder 1358)
  - City University of New York (CUNY) Center on Philanthropy and Civil Society - Emerging Leaders International Fellows Program, 2007 (Box 104, Folder 1359)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Conference - Enhancing China's Contribution to the Development of Sub-Saharan Africa, 2007 (Box 104, Folder 1360-1362)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Conference - Enhancing China's Contribution to the Development of Sub-Saharan Africa, undated (Box 104, Folder 1363)
  - City University of New York (CUNY) Center on Philanthropy and Civil Society - Emerging Leaders International Fellows Program, 2007-2008 (Box 104, Folder 1364)
  - Harvard University Global Equity Initiative (GEI) - Health in China and India: Comparisons, Lessons, and Policies Workshop, 2008 (Box 104, Folder 1365-1366)
  - Japan Foundation Center for Global Partnership (CGP) - Workshop on New Grant Guidelines, 2007-2008 (Box 105, Folder 1367)
  - Center for Strategic and International Studies (CSIS) Conference - U.S. and Chinese Engagement in Africa: Prospects for Improved U.S.-China-Africa Cooperation, 2007 (Box 105, Folder 1368)
  - Harvard University Conference - Rule and Reform in the Giants: China and India Compared, 2007-2008 (Box 105, Folder 1369)
  - Rockefeller Foundation - Dinner Banquet invitation, China Club, Beijing, China, 2007 (Box 105, Folder 1370)
  - National Committee on U.S.-China Relations (NCUSCR) Board of Directors Meeting, 2008 (Box 105, Folder 1371)
  - National Committee on U.S.-China Relations (NCUSCR) Board of Directors Meeting, 2010 (Box 105, Folder 1372)
  - National Committee on U.S.-China Relations (NCUSCR) Executive Committee Meeting, 2009 (Box 105, Folder 1373)
  - China Medical Board (CMB) Board of Trustees Meeting, 2011 (Box 105, Folder 1374-1375)
  - National Committee on U.S.-China Relations (NCUSCR) Executive Committee Meeting, 2008 (Box 105, Folder 1376)
  - Institute of Current World Affairs (ICWA) Board of Trustees Meeting, 2007 (Box 105, Folder 1377)
  - Airplane tickets, 2009 (Box 105, Folder 1378)
  - Asia-Pacific Cities Forum (APCF) Roundtable, 1997-1998 (Box 105, Folder 1379)
  - Asia Society - Foundation for Buddhism in the Twenty-First Century proposal, 2000-2001 (Box 105, Folder 1380)
  - Pacific Forum Center for Strategic and International Studies (CSIS) - U.S. Council on Security Cooperation in the Asia Pacific (USCSCAP) creation, 1992 (Box 106, Folder 1381)
  - Council for Asia-Europe Cooperation (CAEC), 1997-2001 (Box 106, Folder 1382)
  - Council on Security Cooperation in the Asia Pacific (CSCAP), undated (Box 106, Folder 1383)
  - Committee for Economic Development (CED)/National Center for Asia-Pacific Economic Cooperation (APEC) - Pacific Leaders Forum, 1996 (Box 106, Folder 1384)
  - East Asian Development Network (EADN), 2000 (Box 106, Folder 1385)
  - Workers' rights in Asia, 2000-2002 (Box 106, Folder 1386)
  - Bo'ao Forum for Asia, 2001 (Box 106, Folder 1387)
  - Deer Park Initiative: Creating a Foundation for Buddhist Values and Contemporary Society, 2001 (Box 106, Folder 1388)
  - Asian Regional Security, 1997-1998 (Box 106, Folder 1389)
  - Ford Foundation - International Peace and Security Grants, Asian participation, 1994-1999 (Box 106, Folder 1390-1393)
  - Chronicle of Philanthropy articles and Philippines President Fidel Ramos photograph, 1991-1994; File contains a still image of Peter F. Geithner and Fidel Ramos, President of the Philippines. Hand written text on the back of the photograph suggests that the photograph was taken in 1994. (Box 106, Folder 1394)
    The file's contents were found in an envelope addressed to Peter F. Geithner's mother Mrs. Paul H. (Henrietta Schuck) Geithner in Spring House, Pennsylvania.
  - Father's Day card, undated (Box 106, Folder 1395)
  - Ocean City Beach Patrol (OCBP) and other Geithner family history, 1985-2003 (Box 106, Folder 1396)
    File contains printed scans of photographs depicting Peter F. Geithner's brother Paul Geithner during his time as an Ocean City Beach Patrol lifeguard in 1949 and 1951. It also includes a scan of an older photograph of Geithner's relatives that depicts Geithner's mother, Mrs. Paul H. (Henrietta Schuck) Geithner, as a young girl.
  - Asia Pacific Philanthropy Consortium (APPC) Conference - Diaspora Giving: An Agent of Change in Asia Pacific Communities?, 2008; File contains a still image. It is a group photograph of the participants of the Asia Pacific Philanthropy Consortium (APPC) Conference - Diaspora Giving: An Agent of Change in Asia Pacific Communities?. (Box 106, Folder 1397)
  - Asia Pacific Philanthropy Consortium (APPC) Conference - Diaspora Giving: An Agent of Change in Asia Pacific Communities?, 2008 (Box 107, Folder 1398-1401)
  - Australian National University (ANU) East Asia Forum (EAF) Dialogue - Way Forward on Asian Economic and Political Security, 2007-2008 (Box 107, Folder 1402)
  - Harvard University Ash Institute for Democratic Government and Innovation Global Network Conference - Frontiers of Innovation, 2007-2008 (Box 107, Folder 1403-1404)
  - Council on Foundations (COF) Philanthropy Leadership Summit - Panel on China and Philanthropy, 2007-2008 (Box 107, Folder 1405)
  - Hauser Center for Nonprofit Organizations Panel - The Future of Nonprofit Organizations in China, 2008 (Box 107, Folder 1406)
  - Columbia University celebration for Randy Edwards - U.S.-China Legal Cooperation: The Edwards Effect, 1980-2003 (Box 107, Folder 1407)
  - Cairncross Economic Research Foundation (CF) Beijing, 2008 (Box 107, Folder 1408)
  - International Environment Management Senior Training Aid Program, 2008 (Box 107, Folder 1409)
  - Cairncross Economic Research Foundation (CF) Beijing, 2006-2008 (Box 108, Folder 1410-1411)
  - Personal correspondence, 1951-1981; File contains two still images (Folder 1412). One photograph depicts Peter F. Geithner's brother Paul Geithner during his time as an Ocean City Beach Patrol (OCBP) lifeguard in 1951, and the other photograph appears to depict Peter Geithner during his time as a naval aviator. (Box 108, Folder 1412-1416)
- Ford Foundation, Vietnam and China, 1973-1996; 3; 3.96 Cubic Feet 3 LTR size Hollinger boxes and 6 LGL size Hollinger boxes
  Arrangement
  Within the original grouping of material, a clear distinction between records regarding Ford Foundation activities in Vietnam and records regarding Ford Foundation activities in China was observed. This distinction became the basis for the two subseries imposed during processing.
  The series arrangement is as follows:
  Series 3 Subseries 1. Ford Foundation, Vietnam, 1973-1996
  Series 3 Subseries 2. Ford Foundation, China, 1986-1996
  Series consists of a group of records that was originally housed in a set of boxes titled Vietnam and China. These records were all created when Peter F. Geithner worked as the Ford Foundation's Representative for China in Beijing between 1988 and 1990 and when he worked as Ford's Regional Director of Asia Program in New York City between 1990 and 1996. They regard Ford's activities in Vietnam and China in a time period spanning from the late 1980s to the mid-1990s. The series encompasses two subseries. One holds the Vietnam related files and the other holds the China related files.
  The series contains many press and publication items that Geithner received or collected in relation to Vietnam and China. This is particularly true of Series 3 Subseries 2.
  - Ford Foundation, Vietnam, 1973-1996; 1; 1.605 Cubic Feet About 1.75 LTR size Hollinger boxes and 2 LGL size Hollinger boxes
    Subseries documents the Ford Foundation's activities in Vietnam during the time that Peter F. Geithner served as Regional Director of Asia Programs (1990-1996). Most of the records were created through the Foundation's efforts to further develop the Vietnam Program run out of the Bangkok, Thailand Regional Office as well as to open a new Regional Office in Hanoi, Vietnam.
    A significant portion of the subseries consists of loosely organized reports, articles, and guides regarding an assortment of Vietnam-related topics. These subjects include economic and social development, strengthening of diplomatic relations with the U.S. and international relations with other foreign countries, and human rights.
    - Opening Hanoi, Vietnam Office, 1994-1996 (Box 109, Folder 1417)
    - Multi-Foundation delegation to Thailand, Vietnam and Cambodia - Reports, 1989-1991 (Box 109, Folder 1418)
    - Passport, 1973-1978; File contains one still image. A small photograph of Peter F. Geithner was stapled to the back cover of Geithner's passport. (Box 109, Folder 1419)
      Peter F. Geithner's passport was likely displaced from a grouping of material in the previous series at some point prior to processing.
    - Reports and guides regarding Vietnam, 1983-1996 (Box 109, Folder 1420-1426)
    - U.S.-Vietnam Trade Council, 1994-1995 (Box 110, Folder 1427)
    - Vietnam embassy and U.S.-Vietnam diplomatic relations, 1995 (Box 110, Folder 1428)
    - Articles and guides regarding Vietnam, 1993-1995 (Box 110, Folder 1429-1431)
    - Vietnam NGO Directories and other publications regarding Vietnam, 1993-1995 (Box 110, Folder 1432-1433)
    - Reports, articles, and conference materials regarding Vietnam, 1994-1995 (Box 110, Folder 1434-1435)
    - Harvard Institute for International Development (HIID) - In Search of the Dragon's Trail: Economic Reform in Vietnam, 1994 June (Box 111, Folder 1436-1438)
    - Miscellaneous materials regarding Vietnam international relations, 1993-1994 (Box 111, Folder 1439)
    - Mark Sidel letter and Geithner notes, 1993 June (Box 111, Folder 1440)
    - DIALOG Information Services Alert - Vietnam Set to Seek U.S. 20 Billion Aid, Investment by John Rogers, 1993 July 23 (Box 111, Folder 1441)
    - U.S. NGO Forum on Vietnam, Cambodia, and Laos, 1993 (Box 111, Folder 1442)
    - Reports regarding Vietnam, 1993 (Box 111, Folder 1443-1444)
    - Ford Foundation activities in Vietnam, 1991-1993 (Box 111, Folder 1445-1446)
    - Bangkok, Thailand Office Vietnam Program, 1991-1995 (Box 111, Folder 1447-1449)
    - Hanoi, Vietnam Office establishment, 1994-1995 (Box 112, Folder 1450)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting - Vietnam Program, 1993-1994 (Box 112, Folder 1451)
    - Bangkok, Thailand Office Vietnam Program and Hanoi, Vietnam Office establishment, 1973-1995 (Box 112, Folder 1452-1454)
    - Reports regarding Vietnam, 1991-1993 (Box 112, Folder 1455-1456)
    - Ford Foundation activities in Vietnam, 1993-1994 (Box 112, Folder 1457)
  - Ford Foundation, China, 1986-1996; 2; 2.355 Cubic Feet About 1.25 LTR size Hollinger boxes and 4 LGL size Hollinger boxes
    Subseries documents Peter F. Geithner's engagement with various China-related issues during the periods he served as Ford Foundation Representative for China (1988-1990) and Regional Director for Asia Programs (1990-1996). Most of the material consists of newspaper clippings, journal articles, reports, and conference papers, amongst an array of other types of publications and press. These records discuss such topics as economic and political reforms in China, China's international relations and foreign policy (mostly focused on U.S.-China relations), environmental issues and sustainable development, agricultural development, legal system reform, pro-democracy movements, and government repression of intellectuals and political dissidents. Media coverage and academic analysis of the student-led protests at Tiananmen Square and the June Fourth Incident are featured prominently within the subseries as are the coverage and analysis of the international response to the events and China's subsequent economic and political trajectory. A few pieces of correspondence from Geithner help to relay his perspective on the incidents. He wrote the letters in May 1989 to family members as well as to the Ford Office in Dhaka, Bangladesh, just days before the violence occurred.
    Although the subseries does not include many documents that reveal the Ford Foundation's specific program activities in China during the times that Geithner was China Representative or Regional Director for Asia Programs, Geithner's accumulation of these articles and reports suggests that he used these sources to inform his outlook on numerous issues affecting China as well as his program decisions for Ford's activities in the country. There are notes that indicate he requested the material as well as notes that show he received it from colleagues and personal relations who believed that he would be interested in the content. Moreover, Geithner added notes and annotations to many of the papers and articles. A significant portion of the reports are actually drafts that authors submitted to Geithner for his review.
    - The Heritage Foundation - Reform in China after Tiananmen Square by Andrew B. Brick, 1989 (Box 112, Folder 1458)